[
    {"question": "The lighthouse horn moaned, and the sound travelled through the thick fog, reaching the sailors who were enveloped in the greyness", "correct": "The horn made a loud, low sound", "incorrect": "The lighthouse is old"},
    {"question": "A Good Samaritan identified as Mr Li captured the world's attention in May 2014 when he rushed across a street in China to cathc a baby falling from a window.", "correct": "The man generously helped a stranger", "incorrect": "The man was quick-thinking"},
    {"question": "'Someone had better turn on the heating,' Eloise said, sweat glistening on her face", "correct": "The temperature was too warm", "incorrect": "The temperature was too cold"},
    {"question": "For many runners who running barefoot but still want some support and protection, minimalist shoes are the best thing since sliced bread", "correct":"The shoes are a fabulous invention", "incorrect": "The shoes are as soft as freshly baked bread"},
    {"question": "Amy has a lot on her plate: she is at universoty, has a full-time job as a waitress, and volunteers at the animal shelter", "correct": "Amy has many responsibilty", "incorrect": "Amy has worked up an appetite"},
    {"question": "'Sleeping through the cockerel's crowing was no problem,' Theo joked with a yawn", "correct": "Theo slept poorly", "incorrect": "Theo slept well"},
    {"question": "My momma always said life was like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get", "correct": "Life is unpredictable", "incorrect": "Life is the best"},
    {"question": "Isla felt a roller coaster of emotions when she heard the news", "correct": "Isla had varied feelings", "incorrect": "Isla was delighted"},
    {"question": "For spring allergy sufferes, the botanical garden is as pleasant as a traffic jam", "correct": "The botanical garden is unpleasant", "incorrect": "The botanical garden is pleasant"},
    {"question": "Conscience is a man's compass", "correct": "Your conscince guides you to act the right way", "incorrect": "Your conscience shows you where you're headed"}
]